{
  "type": "quiz",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "キャ",
      "answer": "kya"
    },
    {
      "question": "キュ",
      "answer": "kyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "キョ",
      "answer": "kyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "シャ",
      "answer": "sha"
    },
    {
      "question": "シュ",
      "answer": "shu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ショ",
      "answer": "sho"
    },
    {
      "question": "チャ",
      "answer": "cha"
    },
    {
      "question": "チュ",
      "answer": "chu"
    },
    {
      "question": "チョ",
      "answer": "cho"
    },
    {
      "question": "ニャ",
      "answer": "nya"
    },
    {
      "question": "ニュ",
      "answer": "nyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ニョ",
      "answer": "nyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヒャ",
      "answer": "hya"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヒュ",
      "answer": "hyu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヒョ",
      "answer": "hyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "ミャ",
      "answer": "mya"
    },
    {
      "question": "ミュ",
      "answer": "myu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ミョ",
      "answer": "myo"
    },
    {
      "question": "リャ",
      "answer": "rya"
    },
    {
      "question": "リュ",
      "answer": "ryu"
    },
    {
      "question": "リョ",
      "answer": "ryo"
    }
  ]
}
